<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ask Doctor</string>

    <string name="wait_fragment_message">Please Wait ..</string>
    <string name="error_fragment_message">Error Occurred !</string>

    <!--    جراحة العظام-->
    <string name="department_1">Orthopaedic Surgery</string>
    <!--    طب الاسنان-->
    <string name="department_2">Dentistry</string>
    <!--    أخصائي القلي-->
    <string name="department_3">Cardiologist</string>
    <!--    اخصائي طب الاطفال-->
    <string name="department_4">Pediatrics</string>
    <!--    أخصائي الامراض الجلدية-->
    <string name="department_5">Dermatologist</string>
    <!--    جراح تجميل-->
    <string name="department_6">Plastic Surgeon</string>
    <!--    أخصائي اشعة-->
    <string name="department_7">Radiography</string>
    <!--    أخصائي الاورام-->
    <string name="department_8">Oncologist</string>
    <!--طبيب النسا-->
    <string name="department_9">Obstetrics and Gynaecology</string>
    <!--    طبيب المسالك البولية-->
    <string name="department_10">Urologist</string>
    <!--    أخصائي امراض الجهاز الهضمي-->
    <string name="department_11">Gastroenterologist</string>
    <!--    أخصائي امراض الرئة-->
    <string name="department_12">Pulmonologist</string>


    <string name="department_1_Detail">Description \n
        The range of treatments done by orthopedists is enormous. It can cover anything from
        traction to amputation, hand reconstruction to spinal fusion or joint replacements.
        They also treat broken bones, strains and sprains,
        and dislocations. Some specific procedures done by orthopedic surgeons are listed as separate
        entries in this book, including arthroplasty, arthroscopic surgery, bone grafting, fasciotomy,
        fracture repair, kneecap removal, and traction.

        In general orthopedists are attached to a hospital, medical center, trauma center, or free-standing
        surgical center where they work closely with a surgical team including an anesthesiologist and
        surgical nurse. Orthopedic surgery can be performed under general, regional, or local anesthesia.

        Much of the work of the surgeon involves adding foreign material to the body in the form of screws,
        wires, pins, tongs, and prosthetics to hold damaged bones in their proper alignment or to replace
        damaged bone or connective tissue. Great improvements have been made in the development of artificial
        limbs and joints, and in the materials available to repair damage to bones and connective tissue.

        As developments occur in the fields of metallurgy and plastics, changes will take place in orthopedic
        surgery that will allow the surgeon to more nearly duplicate the natural functions of the bones, joints,
        and ligaments, and to more accurately restore damaged parts to their original range of motion.
    </string>

    <string name="department_2_Detail">Description \n
        Dentistry, also known as dental medicine and oral medicine, is a branch of medicine
        that consists of the study, diagnosis, prevention, and treatment of diseases, disorders,
        and conditions of the oral cavity, commonly in the dentition but also the oral mucosa,
        and of adjacent and related structures and tissues, particularly in the maxillofacial
        (jaw and facial) area.

        Although primarily associated with teeth among the general public,
        the field of dentistry or dental medicine is not limited to teeth but includes other aspects of the
        craniofacial complex including the temporomandibular joint and other supporting, muscular,
        lymphatic, nervous, vascular, and anatomical structures.

        Dentistry is often also understood to subsume the now largely defunct medical
        specialty of stomatology (the study of the mouth and its disorders and diseases)
        for which reason the two terms are used interchangeably in certain regions.

        Dental treatments are carried out by a dental team, which often consists of a dentist and dental
        auxiliaries (dental assistants, dental hygienists, dental technicians, as well as dental therapists).
        Most dentists either work in private practices (primary care), dental hospitals or (secondary care)
        institutions (prisons, armed forces bases, etc.).

        The history of dentistry is almost as ancient as the history of humanity and civilization
        with the earliest evidence dating from 7000 BC to 5500 BC.Skeletal remains from Mehgarh
        (now in Pakistan) dated to that time show evidence of teeth having been drilled with flint tools to
        remove decay, a method found to be "surprisingly effective".Dentistry is thought to have been the
        first specialization in medicine.The modern movement of evidence-based dentistry calls for the use
        of high-quality scientific evidence to guide decision-making.
    </string>

    <string name="department_3_Detail">
        What is a Cardiologist?
        Cardiologists are doctors who specialize in diagnosing and treating diseases or
        conditions of the heart and blood vessels—the cardiovascular system.

        Description \n
        Cardiologists are doctors who specialize in diagnosing and treating diseases or
        conditions of the heart and blood vessels—the cardiovascular system. You might also
        visit a cardiologist so you can learn about your risk factors for heart
        disease and find out what measures you can take for better heart health.

        When you are dealing with a complex health condition like heart disease,
        it is important that you find the right match between you and your specialist.

        A diagnosis of heart or vascular disease often begins with your primary care doctor,
        who then refers you to a cardiologist. The cardiologist evaluates your symptoms and your
        medical history and may recommend tests for a more definite diagnosis. Then, your cardiologist
        decides if your condition can be managed under his or her care using medicines or other available treatments.
        If your cardiologist decides that you need surgery, he or she refers you to a cardiovascular surgeon,
        who specializes in operations on the heart, lungs, and blood vessels.

        You remain under the care of your cardiologist even when you are referred to other specialists.
        Cardiology is a complex field, so many cardiologists specialize in different areas.

        All cardiologists are clinical cardiologists who focus on the diagnosis,
        medical management (use of medicines), and prevention of cardiovascular disease.

        Some clinical cardiologists specialize in pediatric cardiology, which means they
        diagnose and treat heart problems in children.

        When clinical cardiologists treat only
        adult patients, they specialize in adult cardiology. Other clinical cardiologists may specialize
        in interventional procedures (balloon angioplasty and stent placement), echocardiography, or
        electrophysiology.

        Cardiologists at the Texas Heart Institute research and develop techniques
        for treating heart and vascular diseases.
    </string>
    <string name="department_4_Detail">Description \n
        Pediatrics is the branch of
        medicine that involves the medical care of infants, children,
        and adolescents.
        The American Academy of Pediatrics recommends people be under pediatric care
        through the age of 21 (though usually only minors are required to be under pediatric care).
        In the United Kingdom, paediatrics covers patients until age 18.Worldwide age limits of
        pediatrics have been trending up year over year. A medical doctor who specializes in
        this area is known as a pediatrician, or paediatrician. The word pediatrics and its cognates mean
        "healer of children"
        Pediatricians work in hospitals and children\'s hospitals particularly
        those working in its subspecialties (e.g. neonatology), and as outpatient primary care physicians.
    </string>
    <string name="department_5_Detail">Description \n
        Dermatology is the branch of medicine dealing with the skin.
        It is a speciality with both medical and surgical aspects.
        A dermatologist is a specialist medical doctor who manages diseases related to skin,
        hair, nails, and some cosmetic problems.
    </string>
    <string name="department_6_Detail">Description \n
        Plastic surgery is a surgical specialty involving the restoration,
        reconstruction, or alteration of the human body.
        It can be divided into two main categories: reconstructive surgery and cosmetic surgery.
        Reconstructive surgery includes craniofacial surgery, hand surgery, microsurgery,
        and the treatment of burns. While reconstructive surgery aims to reconstruct a part of the
        body or improve its functioning, cosmetic (or aesthetic) surgery aims at improving the appearance of it.
    </string>
    <string name="department_7_Detail">Description \n
        Radiography is an imaging technique using X-rays, gamma rays, or similar ionizing radiation
        and non-ionizing radiation to view the internal form of an object.
        Applications of radiography include medical radiography ("diagnostic" and "therapeutic")
        and industrial radiography. Similar techniques are used in airport security
        (where "body scanners" generally use backscatter X-ray). To create an image in conventional
        radiography, a beam of X-rays is produced by an X-ray generator and is projected toward the object.
        A certain amount of the X-rays or other radiation is absorbed by the object, dependent on the object\'s
        density and structural composition. The X-rays that pass through the object are captured
        behind the object by a detector (either photographic film or a digital detector).
        The generation of flat two dimensional images by this technique is called projectional radiography.
        In computed tomography (CT scanning) an X-ray source and its associated detectors rotate around the
        subject which itself moves through the conical X-ray beam produced. Any given point within
        the subject is crossed from many directions by many different beams at different times.
        Information regarding attenuation of these beams is collated and subjected to computation to
        generate two dimensional images in three planes (axial, coronal, and sagittal) which can be further
        processed to produce a three dimensional image.
    </string>
    <string name="department_8_Detail">Description \n
        Oncology is a branch of medicine that deals with the prevention, diagnosis,
        and treatment of cancer. A medical professional who practices oncology is an oncologist.
        The name\'s etymological origin is the Greek word ὄγκος (óngkos), meaning 1.
        "burden, volume, mass" and 2. "barb", and the Greek word λόγος (logos), meaning "study".
        The neoclassical term oncology was used from 1618, initially in neo-Greek,
        in cognizance of Galen\'s work on abnormal tumors, De tumoribus præter naturam (Περὶ τῶν παρὰ φύσιν ὄγκων).
        Cancer survival has improved due to three main components:
        improved prevention efforts to reduce exposure to risk factors (e.g., tobacco smoking and alcohol
        consumption),improved screening of several cancers (allowing for earlier diagnosis),
        and improvements in treatment.
        Cancers are often managed through discussion on multi-disciplinary cancer conferences
        where medical oncologists, surgical oncologists, radiation oncologist, pathologists,
        radiologists, and organ specific oncologists meet to find the best possible management
        for an individual patient considering the physical, social, psychological, emotional,
        and financial status of the patient.[9] It is very important for oncologists to keep updated with
        respect to the latest advancements in oncology, as changes in management of cancer are quite common.
        Because a cancer diagnosis can cause distress and anxiety, clinicians may use
        a number of strategies such as SPIKES for delivering the bad news.
    </string>
    <string name="department_9_Detail">Description \n
        Obstetrics and gynaecology (British English) or obstetrics and gynecology
        (American English) is the medical specialty that encompasses the two subspecialties of obstetrics
        (covering pregnancy, childbirth, and the postpartum period) and gynecology
        (covering the health of the female reproductive system – vagina, uterus, ovaries, and breasts).
        It is commonly abbreviated as OB-GYN or OB/GYN in US English and Canadian English,
        and as obs and gynae or O and G in British English.
        Postgraduate training programs for both fields are usually combined,
        preparing the practicing obstetrician-gynecologist to be adept both at the care of
        female reproductive organs\' health and at the management of pregnancy, although many
        doctors go on to develop subspecialty interests in one field or the other.
    </string>
    <string name="department_10_Detail">Description \n
        Urology , also known as genitourinary surgery,
        is the branch of medicine that focuses on surgical and medical diseases of the male and female
        urinary-tract system and the male reproductive organs. Organs under the domain of urology include
        the kidneys, adrenal glands, ureters, urinary bladder, urethra, and the male reproductive organs
        (testes, epididymis, vas deferens, seminal vesicles, prostate, and penis).
        The urinary and reproductive tracts are closely linked, and disorders of one often affect the other.
        Thus a major spectrum of the conditions managed in urology exists under the domain of genitourinary
        disorders. Urology combines the management of medical (i.e., non-surgical) conditions, such as
        urinary-tract infections and benign prostatic hyperplasia, with the management of surgical conditions
        such as bladder or prostate cancer, kidney stones, congenital abnormalities, traumatic injury, and stress
        incontinence.
        Urological techniques include minimally invasive robotic and laparoscopic surgery, laser-assisted surgeries,
        and other scope-guided procedures. Urologists receive training in open and minimally invasive surgical
        techniques, employing real-time ultrasound guidance, fiber-optic endoscopic equipment, and
        various lasers in the treatment of multiple benign and malignant conditions.Urology is
        closely related to (and urologists often collaborate with the practitioners of) oncology, nephrology,
        gynaecology, andrology, pediatric surgery, colorectal surgery, gastroenterology, and endocrinology.
        Urology is one of the most competitive and highly sought surgical specialties for physicians, with new urologists
        comprising less than 1.5% of United States medical-school graduates each year.
        Urologists are physicians which have specialized in the field after completing their general degree in medicine.
        Upon successful completion of a residency program, many urologists choose to undergo further advanced
        training in a subspecialty area of expertise through a fellowship lasting an additional 12 to 36 months.
        Subspecialties may include: urologic surgery, urologic oncology and urologic oncological surgery,
        endourology and endourologic surgery, urogynecology and urogynecologic surgery, reconstructive urologic
        surgery (a form of reconstructive surgery), minimally-invasive urologic surgery, pediatric urology and
        pediatric urologic surgery (including adolescent urology, the treatment of premature or delayed puberty,
        and the treatment of congenital urological syndromes, malformations, and deformations), transplant urology
        (the field of transplant medicine and surgery concerned with transplantation of organs such as the kidneys,
        bladder tissue, ureters, and, recently, penises), voiding dysfunction, paruresis, neurourology,
        and androurology and sexual medicine. Additionally, some urologists supplement their fellowships with a
        master\'s degree (2–3 years) or with a Ph.D. (4–6 years) in related topics to prepare them for academic
        as well as focused clinical employment.
    </string>
    <string name="department_11_Detail">Description \n
        Gastroenterology is the branch of medicine focused on the digestive system and its disorders.
        Diseases affecting the gastrointestinal tract, which include the organs from mouth into anus, along the
        alimentary canal, are the focus of this speciality. Physicians practicing in this field are called
        gastroenterologists. They have usually completed about eight years of pre-medical and medical education,
        a year-long internship (if this is not a part of the residency), three years of an internal medicine
        residency, and three years in the gastroenterology fellowship. Gastroenterologists perform a number
        of diagnostic and therapeutic procedures including colonoscopy, esophagogastroduodenoscopy (EGD),
        endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography (ERCP), endoscopic ultrasound (EUS), and liver biopsy.
        Some gastroenterology trainees will complete a "fourth-year" (although this is often their seventh year
        of graduate medical education) in transplant hepatology, advanced interventional endoscopy, inflammatory
        bowel disease, motility, or other topics.
        Advanced endoscopy, sometimes called interventional or surgical endoscopy, is a sub-specialty of
        gastroenterology that focuses on advanced endoscopic techniques for the treatment of pancreatic,
        hepatobiliary, and gastrointestinal disease. Interventional gastroenterologists typically undergo an
        additional year of rigorous training in advanced endoscopic techniques including endoscopic retrograde
        cholangiopancreatography, endoscopic ultrasound-guided diagnostic and interventional procedures,
        and advanced resection techniques including endoscopic mucosal resection and endoscopic submucosal
        dissection. Additionally, the performance of endoscopic bariatric procedures is also performed by some
        advanced endoscopists.
        Hepatology, or hepatobiliary medicine, encompasses the study of the liver, pancreas, and biliary
        tree, and is traditionally considered a sub-specialty of gastroenterology, while proctology
        encompasses disorders of the anus, rectum, and colon and is considered a sub-specialty of general surgery.
    </string>
    <string name="department_12_Detail">Description \n
        Pulmonology is a medical specialty that deals with diseases involving the respiratory tract.
        It is also known as respirology, respiratory medicine, or chest medicine in some countries and areas.
        Pulmonology is considered a branch of internal medicine, and is related to intensive care medicine.
        Pulmonology often involves managing patients who need life support and mechanical ventilation.
        Pulmonologists are specially trained in diseases and conditions of the chest, particularly pneumonia,
        asthma, tuberculosis, emphysema, and complicated chest infections.
    </string>


    <string name="no_internet_connection" translatable="false">No internet is available</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_connection" translatable="false">Mobile data enabled</string>
    <string name="wifi_connection" translatable="false">Wifi enabled</string>

    <string name="required">Required</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="emailKey">EmailOfSharedPreferences</string>
    <string name="passwordKey">PasswordOfSharedPreferences</string>
    <string name="doctorKey">DoctorOfSharedPreferences</string>
    <string name="title_activity_department_detail">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="sendDepartmentDetails">SELECTED DEPARTMENT DATA</string>

    <string name="publicQuestions">Public Questions</string>
    <string name="SentDoctor">Sent Doctor</string>

    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>MALE</item>
        <item>FEMALE</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>